[
 {
   "No": 1,
   "Quiz question": "In which year did Maradona score a goal with his hand?",
   "Answer": "1986"
 },
 {
   "No": 2,
   "Quiz question": "What is the national sport in Japan?",
   "Answer": "Sumo Wrestling"
 },
 {
   "No": 3,
   "Quiz question": "How many minutes is a rugby match?",
   "Answer": "80 Minutes"
 },
 {
   "No": 4,
   "Quiz question": "In which country were the first Olympic Games held?",
   "Answer": "Greece"
 },
 {
   "No": 5,
   "Quiz question": "How many players are on each side of the net in beach volleyball?",
   "Answer": "Two players"
 },
 {
   "No": 6,
   "Quiz question": "What should you do in swordplay when you break your saber?",
   "Answer": "Replace it"
 },
 {
   "No": 7,
   "Quiz question": "How matches did Mohammed Ali lose in his career?",
   "Answer": "Only one"
 },
 {
   "No": 8,
   "Quiz question": "How long is an Olympic swimming pool?",
   "Answer": "Fifty meters"
 },
 {
   "No": 9,
   "Quiz question": "At what number does one begin when playing Darts?",
   "Answer": "The number 501"
 },
 {
   "No": 10,
   "Quiz question": "Which car won Fernando Alonso his first tittle in Formula 1 with?",
   "Answer": "Renault"
 },
 {
   "No": 11,
   "Quiz question": "Who was the champion of the Tour de France from 1999 to 2005?",
   "Answer": "Lance Armstrong"
 },
 {
   "No": 12,
   "Quiz question": "Which cyclist was also called the cannibal?",
   "Answer": "Eddy Merckx"
 },
 {
   "No": 13,
   "Quiz question": "How many players has a hockey team got on the ice?",
   "Answer": "Six players"
 },
 {
   "No": 14,
   "Quiz question": "What was the Olympic city of 1992 ?",
   "Answer": "Barcelona"
 },
 {
   "No": 15,
   "Quiz question": "What is the largest stadium in the world ?",
   "Answer": "Azteca Stadium in Mexico city"
 },
 {
   "No": 16,
   "Quiz question": "Which two sports are practiced on a green table ?",
   "Answer": "Billiards and ping-pong"
 },
 {
   "No": 17,
   "Quiz question": "In which country is the Interlagos F1-circuit ?",
   "Answer": "Brazil"
 },
 {
   "No": 18,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of the Barcelona football stadium ?",
   "Answer": "Camp Nou"
 },
 {
   "No": 19,
   "Quiz question": "Where were the Olympic Games held in 1996 ?",
   "Answer": "Atlanta"
 },
 {
   "No": 20,
   "Quiz question": "What is the nickname of the Belgian national soccer team?",
   "Answer": "Red devils"
 },
 {
   "No": 21,
   "Quiz question": "Which ball is worth the most points in English snooker?",
   "Answer": "The black ball"
 },
 {
   "No": 22,
   "Quiz question": "Which nickname has Florence Griffith got?",
   "Answer": "Fast Flo"
 },
 {
   "No": 23,
   "Quiz question": "What is called a yoga posture?",
   "Answer": "Asana"
 },
 {
   "No": 24,
   "Quiz question": "In which sport can you win the Davis Cup?",
   "Answer": "Tennis"
 },
 {
   "No": 25,
   "Quiz question": "Which popular fitness method was invented by a German?",
   "Answer": "Pilates"
 },
 {
   "No": 26,
   "Quiz question": "How many times has Michael Schumacher been a Formula 1 champion?",
   "Answer": "Seven times"
 }
]